

Bersam Karbasion

Web & Mobile Developer



Mirdamad St., Isfahan, Isfahan, 8136954861Islamic Republic of Iran



info@bersam.org



www.bersam.org



@bersamk

Profile:

My name is Bersam Karbasion (pronounced as [ber sa:m] in English and written as: "برسام كرباسيون" in Persian). I was born in Iran and since then I have lived in Iran. I am a kind of young programmer who tries to learn new things and to be well-experienced in programming. Moreover, working in Free Software field(s) is one of the things who I tend to do constantly. By a quick search you can find me in Wikipedia editors too! Also check my scorecard at smarterer.

Skills:

- Linux
- Git
- PHP
- Python
- MvSQL
- HTML 5 / CSS 3
- JavaScript / JQuery
- WordPress / Dokuwiki / Mediawiki / Joomla ...

Familiar:

- C++ (Learning)
- Assembly (ASEM-51)
- Blender
- GIMP
- Android/JAVA

Experience:

Web & Mobile Developer

Cvas

September 2013 - Now

CVAS team is young and professional, which use on-edge technology for their services. in CVAS, I mostly make Android Applications for other services we provide and I make RESTful API for other services or customers.

Web Developer

Jooyeshgar

February 2013 - September 2013

Jooyeshgar (Jooyeshgar Pardis Eram) is a web design company since 2000. Jooyeshgar's services include custom website design, web application development, online booking system, web portal development, ecommerce solutions and etc.

Web Developer

Metacomplex

June 2012 - February 2013

Metacomplex (Isfahan Communication Development Complex) is one of the biggest companies in Isfahan. People consider Metaco as a training center, but Metaco is active in many other fields. Web Development is one of them.

Me and Linux (Persian) Weblog:

Education: Sheikh Bahaei University

Behesht St.

Baharestan, Isfahan, Islamic Republic of Iran

Computer Science 2012 - Present

shbu.ac.ir



Social Icons by Paul Robert Lloyd, Profile & Download Icons by Drylcons, Phone Icon by ComFi Telecom. All used under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike license: http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0/